nukepedia.com 2019-10-18

# Privacy Policy - Nukepedia

**OHUfx ltd.** ("We") are committed to respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with [our terms of use](https://www.nukepedia.com/terms-of-use) and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

## **I** **NFORMATION** ******WE** ******MAY** ******COLLECT** ******FROM** ******YOU**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information that you provide (for example by filling in forms) to our site www.nukepedia.com (“our site”). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.

If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, and the resources that you access.

**IP** **ADDRESSES** ******AND** ******COOKIES**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:

To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.

To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to your individual interests.

To speed up your searches.

To recognise you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

## **YOUR** ******PERSONAL** ******DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside New Zealand. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.

## **U** **SES** ******MADE** ******OF** ******THE** ******INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.

To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.

To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form).

## **D** **ISCLOSURE** ******OF** ******YOUR** ******INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply [our terms of use](https://www.nukepedia.com/terms-of-use) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of **OHUfx** , our contributors, visitors or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## **Y** **OUR** ******RIGHTS**

You may ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes: we will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from other websites.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites may have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for those websites or their policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## **A** **CCESS** ******TO** ******INFORMATION**

If you request access to information held about you we may charge a fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information.

## **C** **HANGES** ******TO** ******OUR** ******PRIVACY** ******POLICY**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

## **C** **ONTACT**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [admin@nukepedia.com](mailto:admin@nukepedia.com).
